<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="hide-it.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<item>
	<title>10 Rillington Place</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066730</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>10 Rillington Place</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The story of British serial killer John Christie, who committed most or all of his crimes in the titular terraced house, and the miscarriage of justice involving Timothy Evans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aQP2rSIciaeb2FGPeOQIWsCysts.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hW03BfIUb9UCpaakOO5S7o7VLB0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>1917</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt8579674</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>1917</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>At the height of the First World War, two young British soldiers must cross enemy territory and deliver a message that will stop a deadly attack on hundreds of soldiers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iZf0KyrE25z1sage4SYFLCCrMi9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2lBOQK06tltt8SQaswgb8d657Mv.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>24 Hour Party People</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0274309</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>24 Hour Party People</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Manchester, 1976. Tony Wilson is an ambitious but frustrated local TV news reporter looking for a way to make his mark. After witnessing a life-changing concert by a band known as the Sex Pistols, he persuades his station to televise one of their performances, and soon Manchester's punk groups are clamoring for him to manage them. Riding the wave of a musical revolution, Wilson and his friends create the legendary Factory Records label and The Hacienda club.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8f50NQ1wz6hdxfCISCPV8XQ6DII.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ucRD8UUr5tllltg3ZTWoXOyPXyJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>28 Weeks Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0463854</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Weeks Later</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The inhabitants of the British Isles have lost their battle against the onslaught of disease, as the deadly rage virus has killed every citizen there. Six months later, a group of Americans dare to set foot on the isles, convinced the danger has come and gone. But it soon becomes all too clear that the scourge continues to live, waiting to pounce on its next victims.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ja8nzgtzhJq0vtX3BJcnbceIxCF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/PN7yjmQdmG0J62jsrtmrPi8ezK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Bridge Too Far</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075784</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Bridge Too Far</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Operation Market Garden, September 1944. The Allies attempt to capture several strategically important bridges in the Netherlands in the hope of breaking the German lines.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lszOk3Xmh7qpLaM9J4K9E6ADLk1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/26feWH2NF8XqxuMzfkJTp9T5dfQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Clockwork Orange</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066921</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Clockwork Orange</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In a near-future Britain, young Alexander DeLarge and his pals get their kicks beating and raping anyone they please. When not destroying the lives of others, Alex swoons to the music of Beethoven. The state, eager to crack down on juvenile crime, gives an incarcerated Alex the option to undergo an invasive procedure that'll rob him of all personal agency. In a time when conscience is a commodity, can Alex change his tune?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4sHeTAp65WrSSuc05nRBKddhBxO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bR4U9n9YnZOvBUhOUNl316UNEyh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Fish Called Wanda</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095159</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Fish Called Wanda</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A diamond advocate is attempting to steal a collection of diamonds, yet troubles arise when he realizes that he is not the only one after the diamonds.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hkSGFNVfEEUXFCxRZDITFHVhUlu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y8HaV1Ntr6nHmKxZ29B7DwxwvNU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Hard Day's Night</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0058182</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Hard Day's Night</title>
	<year>1964</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Capturing John Lennon, Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr in their electrifying element, 'A Hard Day's Night' is a wildly irreverent journey through this pastiche of a day in the life of The Beatles during 1964. The band have to use all their guile and wit to avoid the pursuing fans and press to reach their scheduled television performance, in spite of Paul's troublemaking grandfather and Ringo's arrest.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0kHz7m64wDzvPLmkUl36pN2IHP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9hWiNbvLR3nPDanTdEWOc4EeBGp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Kind of Loving</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056141</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Kind of Loving</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>As Vic Brown vacillates between infatuation and disinterest for his co-worker Ingrid Rothwell, she  finds out that she is pregnant and Vic has to reconcile how he thought his life would go with what life actually has in store for him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ArE4ox7MWPIJcGZYonvRpOYPlTT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fqRjyw9MceJrTj9Z3ppEWPeYq09.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Taste of Honey</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0055506</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Taste of Honey</title>
	<year>1961</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A working class girl struggles to create a life for herself with her gay co-worker after becoming pregnant from a one-night stand with a black sailor.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5psrZNVZ9E6Eck7OtpO47A8zTbQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tGT8187UOFJmMYVsyyjDjXsfaVI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>About Time</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2194499</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>About Time</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The night after another unsatisfactory New Year's party, Tim's father tells his son that the men in his family have always had the ability to travel through time. They can't change history, but they can change what happens and has happened in their own lives. Thus begins the start of a lesson in learning to appreciate life itself as it is, as it comes, and most importantly, the people living alongside us.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iR1bVfURbN7r1C46WHFbwCkVve.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qo7QDVyJwwM9pMo7huxvV7oX84Y.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ali G Indahouse</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0284837</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ali G Indahouse</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Ali G unwittingly becomes a pawn in the evil Chancellor's plot to overthrow the Prime Minister of Great Britain. However, instead of bringing the Prime Minister down, Ali is embraced by the nation as the voice of youth and 'realness', making the Prime Minister and his government more popular than ever.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pjKvQrVpekshVM6DUDOt3ImhAVH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ll5ktqAG3EOlCS8bpyoC0kYSSe9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Atonement</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0783233</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Atonement</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>As a 13-year-old, fledgling writer Briony Tallis irrevocably changes the course of several lives when she accuses her older sister's lover of a crime he did not commit.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hMRIyBjPzxaSXWM06se3OcNjIQa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cXqGiKrIQRYFCp5UgrP8dYdBmKH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Belfast</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt12789558</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Belfast</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Buddy is a young boy on the cusp of adolescence, whose life is filled with familial love, childhood hijinks, and a blossoming romance. Yet, with his beloved hometown caught up in increasing turmoil, his family faces a momentous choice: hope the conflict will pass or leave everything they know behind for a new life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3mInLZyPOVLsZRsBwNHi3UJXXnm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4KLlHifB1kgMtWl3YnY8JinOj65.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Billy Liar</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056868</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Billy Liar</title>
	<year>1963</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young Englishman dreams of escaping from his working class family and dead-end job as an undertaker's assistant. A number of indiscretions cause him to lie in order to avoid the penalties. His life turns into a mess and he has an opportunity to run away and leave it all behind.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8YUzVyN3HdedaK7oGVf2nVrsf4R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GnuKyGYNgIxTd9jC5SZZFSIbSP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Bohemian Rhapsody</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1727824</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bohemian Rhapsody</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock 'n' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury's increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lHu1wtNaczFPGFDTrjCSzeLPTKN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7mmXWuBeNJiBO0NIOUWOuFve4Tb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Brief Encounter</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0037558</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Brief Encounter</title>
	<year>1945</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Returning home from a shopping trip to a nearby town, bored suburban housewife Laura Jesson is thrown by happenstance into an acquaintance with virtuous doctor Alec Harvey. Their casual friendship soon develops during their weekly visits into something more emotionally fulfilling than either expected, and they must wrestle with the potential havoc their deepening relationship would have on their lives and the lives of those they love.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jC9EwLJcGhYMSQAHu2LxkKN5v7O.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vKvoOlhhaZCsiGQDvaZQqyGq1oA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Chariots of Fire</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0082158</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Chariots of Fire</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the class-obsessed and religiously divided UK of the early 1920s, two determined young runners train for the 1924 Paris Olympics. Eric Liddell, a devout Christian born to Scottish missionaries in China, sees running as part of his worship of God's glory and refuses to train or compete on the Sabbath. Harold Abrahams overcomes anti-Semitism and class bias, but neglects his beloved sweetheart in his single-minded quest.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qnRaum8k0HqGRml2i7OawFqUtEb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qgPYU8xDYiZPKapK0sOvfIEKRtH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Children of Men</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0206634</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Children of Men</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 2027, in a chaotic world in which humans can no longer procreate, a former activist agrees to help transport a miraculously pregnant woman to a sanctuary at sea, where her child's birth may help scientists save the future of humankind.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k9IAS4TehZFcKi4HVByxZNPfqex.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z8FzomPxfCb2nv827VWLSI6oYiB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Darkest Hour</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4555426</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Darkest Hour</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A thrilling and inspiring true story begins on the eve of World War II as, within days of becoming Prime Minister of Great Britain, Winston Churchill must face one of his most turbulent and defining trials: exploring a negotiated peace treaty with Nazi Germany, or standing firm to fight for the ideals, liberty and freedom of a nation. As the unstoppable Nazi forces roll across Western Europe and the threat of invasion is imminent, and with an unprepared public, a skeptical King, and his own party plotting against him, Churchill must withstand his darkest hour, rally a nation, and attempt to change the course of world history.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z0K8uoNbrYKkbaP7wIeadJ4BmSL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zXwFJMwvQcJFitP9GcHZvHAHGe8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dead Man's Shoes</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0419677</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dead Man's Shoes</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A soldier returns home to his small town and exacts a deadly revenge on the thugs who tormented his dimwitted brother while he was away.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lI7dsNWL8Ue5n5dB5dAdQhTktPe.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gaCrwIiqB2S0w6xDOSa76NUIawU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dunkirk</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5013056</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dunkirk</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The story of the miraculous evacuation of Allied soldiers from Belgium, Britain, Canada and France, who were cut off and surrounded by the German army from the beaches and harbour of Dunkirk between May 26th and June 4th 1940 during World War II.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ebSnODDg9lbsMIaWg2uAbjn7TO5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eXYbyOx6GFvmpOJl6AS8QxXeIYE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>East Is East</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0166175</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>East Is East</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1971 Salford fish-and-chip shop owner George Khan expects his family to follow his strict Pakistani Muslim ways. But his children, with an English mother and having been born and brought up in Britain, increasingly see themselves as British and start to reject their father's rules on dress, food, religion, and living in general.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tDchJ4mB23vGgwdQCmq9FCQ4W23.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dxsMt5JspjPdMk59nap00Z8p4nx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Educating Rita</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0085478</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Educating Rita</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rita, a witty 26-year-old hairdresser, wants to 'discover' herself, so she joins the Open University where she meets the disillusioned professor of literature, Dr. Frank Bryant. His marriage has failed, his new girlfriend is having an affair with his best friend and he can't get through the day without downing a bottle or two of whisky. What Frank needs is a challenge... and along comes Rita.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xwxgiRzw2zxzWNIYp98faJ0rUy5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4WaqsTQUhGzRRuuY7FXPVM1lLda.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fish Tank</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1232776</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fish Tank</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mia is a rebellious teenager on the verge of being kicked out of school. Her hard-partying mother, Joanne, neglects Mia's welfare in favor of her own, and her younger sister hangs out with a much older crowd. Sparks fly between Mia and Connor, Joanne's new boyfriend, and he encourages Mia to pursue her interest in dance. As the boundaries of the relationships become blurred, Mia and Joanne compete for Connor's affection.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q4Q6ZQzV016w8CGn6idGrtF7h7t.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kUa5p73cjzDXoqB6SKncfYKmMu2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Four Lions</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1341167</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Four Lions</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A group of Muslim men living in Sheffield hatch an inept plan to become suicide bombers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lU9WFPChJ1CsD5kZuYoCdoAlbRd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lwP2JtnhoKxhLoOo2u9jW3c3RIB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Gandhi</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083987</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Gandhi</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the early years of the 20th century, Mohandas K. Gandhi, a British-trained lawyer, forsakes all worldly possessions to take up the cause of Indian independence. Faced with armed resistance from the British government, Gandhi adopts a policy of 'passive resistance', endeavouring to win freedom for his people without resorting to bloodshed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rOXftt7SluxskrFrvU7qFJa5zeN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gum3tuO1zKHBdElSQPS08PJ1w67.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Get Carter</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0067128</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Get Carter</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jack Carter is a small-time hood working in London. When word reaches him of his brother's death, he travels to Newcastle to attend the funeral. Refusing to accept the police report of suicide, Carter seeks out his brother’s friends and acquaintances to learn who murdered his sibling and why.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zuVdznULyEowTLIFjEVq5turMPc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pRBCb6Hs6Xo4diXwpnBTcwMizE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Goodbye, Mr. Chips</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0031385</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Goodbye, Mr. Chips</title>
	<year>1939</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A shy British teacher looks back nostalgically at his long career, taking note of the people who touched his life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qjRdqKBmaHZrQAWpYkiXVnJRJXn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d9ThwpGXncwXLGk3jNOK1Xyrv5M.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Green Street Hooligans</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0385002</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Green Street Hooligans</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After being wrongfully expelled from Harvard University, American Matt Buckner flees to his sister's home in England. Once there, he is befriended by her charming and dangerous brother-in-law, Pete Dunham, and introduced to the underworld of British football hooliganism. Matt learns to stand his ground through a friendship that develops against the backdrop of this secret and often violent world. 'Green Street Hooligans' is a story of loyalty, trust and the sometimes brutal consequences of living close to the edge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tfLj69EoP1b8ZWfLyg5FGJ5LC38.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qE8b8aCKEoZxDmS6PITSc4EiQ0F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Grimsby</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3381008</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Grimsby</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Wrongfully accused and on the run, a top MI6 assassin joins forces with his long-lost, football hooligan brother to save the world from a sinister plot.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/snwjRGxnPGDbtjfl0lmqLbextot.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qrLfuJ56J0hwTJYgiOXKY0UUolf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Holiday on the Buses</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071613</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Holiday on the Buses</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Due to a female passenger falling out of her top whilst running for the bus Stan is distracted and crashes the bus resulting in the depot managers car being written off. As a result Stan, Jack and Blakey are fired. Stan and Jack soon get new jobs as a bus crew at a Pontins holiday resort but discover that Blakey has also gotten a job there as the chief security guard.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3ewJwuY28E4RzCRf2lklwvzPrsK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ePMrWBFymjeEN2nbQsjUdfnusCt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hot Fuzz</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0425112</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hot Fuzz</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>As a former London constable, Nicholas Angel finds it difficult to adapt to his new assignment in the sleepy British village of Sandford. Not only does he miss the excitement of the big city, but he also has a well-meaning oaf for a partner. However, when a series of grisly accidents rocks Sandford, Angel smells something rotten in the idyllic village.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zPib4ukTSdXvHP9pxGkFCe34f3y.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zuskekrfW3gj9ttXNVhfdHe5n22.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>How Green Was My Valley</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0033729</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>How Green Was My Valley</title>
	<year>1941</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>At the turn of the century in a Welsh mining village, the Morgans (he stern, she gentle) raise coal-mining sons and hope their youngest will find a better life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8N7OmxBqjRVUrqergUduGgr6exy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ucQESsrG63LsA5HD70aaPxEyORk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>I, Daniel Blake</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5168192</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>I, Daniel Blake</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A middle aged carpenter, who requires state welfare after injuring himself, is joined by a single mother in a similar scenario.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nu3WVABXz2W85N6JXTZOT1aWS3b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2BHjCq5fonp5r16qxGZ9VS3pHtw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>In the Name of the Father</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107207</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>In the Name of the Father</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A small time thief from Belfast, Gerry Conlon, is falsely implicated in the IRA bombing of a pub that kills several people while he is in London. He and his four friends are coerced by British police into confessing their guilt. Gerry's father and other relatives in London are also implicated in the crime. He spends fifteen years in prison with his father trying to prove his innocence.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3NcIkKxaO2SmRVsG1v50XhtmL0f.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jgD5rT4pijE7Hm596A6rp5jalXE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kes</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0064541</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Kes</title>
	<year>1970</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young, English working-class boy spends his free time caring for and training his pet falcon.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r1FMq75irhsQBVGjXhPU4xA9SDo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hmzvI2zS3a7DrhfVgIibohpNQLW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lawrence of Arabia</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056172</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lawrence of Arabia</title>
	<year>1962</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The story of British officer T.E. Lawrence's mission to aid the Arab tribes in their revolt against the Ottoman Empire during the First World War. Lawrence becomes a flamboyant, messianic figure in the cause of Arab unity but his psychological instability threatens to undermine his achievements.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AiAm0EtDvyGqNpVoieRw4u65vD1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mx2jS5Kaa5rmaldEFzKeKpDN9Q2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Layer Cake</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0375912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Layer Cake</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When a seemingly straight-forward drug deal goes awry, XXXX has to break his die-hard rules and turn up the heat, not only to outwit the old regime and come out on top, but to save his own skin...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fSE9AI2Ytz2mBZjelc32NiZGcj9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a8230eNW59hSOkj5XrRpzMMh0WT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Life of Brian</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079470</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Life of Brian</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Brian Cohen is an average young Jewish man, but through a series of ridiculous events, he gains a reputation as the Messiah. When he's not dodging his followers or being scolded by his shrill mother, the hapless Brian has to contend with the pompous Pontius Pilate and acronym-obsessed members of a separatist movement. Rife with Monty Python's signature absurdity, the tale finds Brian's life paralleling Biblical lore, albeit with many more laughs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lSSA64WF0M0BXnjwr2quMh6shCl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gbLeMznYBlI7rsyg766oBwkdo2w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120735</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A card shark and his unwillingly-enlisted friends need to make a lot of cash quick after losing a sketchy poker match. To do this they decide to pull a heist on a small-time gang who happen to be operating out of the flat next door.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8kSerJrhrJWKLk1LViesGcnrUPE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cXQH2u7wUIX1eoIdEj51kHXoWhX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>McVicar</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0081144</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>McVicar</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>John McVicar was a London Bad Boy. he graduated to armed bank robbery and was Britain's "Public Enemy No. 1". He was captured and put into a high security prison. Will even the highest security prison be able to hold him? This is the true story of his life, his criminal exploits and his eventual rehabilitation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uKftNDT2xisKn2QllKNpCkJ9F3y.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wjwdZinFCWNJDafi4jDc45FxTtc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Me Before You</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2674426</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Me Before You</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A small town girl is caught between dead-end jobs. A high-profile, successful man becomes wheelchair bound following an accident. The man decides his life is not worth living until the girl is hired for six months to be his new caretaker. Worlds apart and trapped together by circumstance, the two get off to a rocky start. But the girl becomes determined to prove to the man that life is worth living and as they embark on a series of adventures together, each finds their world changing in ways neither of them could begin to imagine.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Ia3dzj5LnCj1ZBdlVeJrbKJQxG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7jjwdoIVPJp7gcDo9uE1sVZi2Rs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071853</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>King Arthur, accompanied by his squire, recruits his Knights of the Round Table, including Sir Bedevere the Wise, Sir Lancelot the Brave, Sir Robin the Not-Quite-So-Brave-As-Sir-Lancelot and Sir Galahad the Pure. On the way, Arthur battles the Black Knight who, despite having had all his limbs chopped off, insists he can still fight. They reach Camelot, but Arthur decides not  to enter, as "it is a silly place".</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8AVb7tyxZRsbKJNOTJHQZl7JYWO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nWkxOXpctN2NuToGzwCSdFdiht0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mutiny on the Buses</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0068981</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mutiny on the Buses</title>
	<year>1972</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Bus driver Stan Butler agrees to marry Suzy, much to the anguish of Mum, her son-in-law, Arthur, and daughter Olive. How, they wonder, will they ever manage without Stan's money coming in? Then Arthur is sacked, and Stan agrees to delay the wedding. Meanwhile, he hits on an idea: Arthur should learn to drive a bus. Somehow he does just that, and even gets a job. Stan then blackmails the Depot Manager into giving him the job of driver on the new money-making Special Tours Bus. A great idea ...if only the inspector hadn't taken Stan on his trial run to the Windsor Safari Park</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4XK9oMfe4Ae53JtXGH45d4c26dG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bOxG9sJ8g9BjX5OVOV9kCR0FDXP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>My Left Foot: The Story of Christy Brown</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0097937</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>My Left Foot: The Story of Christy Brown</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In this true story told through flashbacks, Christy Brown is born with crippling cerebral palsy into a poor, working-class Irish family. Able only to control movement in his left foot and to speak in guttural sounds, he is mistakenly believed to have a intellectual disability for the first ten years of his life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/GRAAl0bMQFoFIjV3aunc5jsM5u.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h7wlgMBLhHFcHbn0OfhJNwRd42R.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Northern Soul</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1837613</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Northern Soul</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in 1974, an authentic and uplifting tale of two friends whose horizons are opened up by the discovery of black American soul music.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ajnHRtHP2QUtoJ7VeAVP3E9gaI8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xSmW93b4LhVTbOp4HYRsooCYviI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nowhere Boy</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1266029</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Nowhere Boy</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The drama tells the story of John Lennon's teenage years in Liverpool and the start of his journey to becoming a successful musician. The story also examines the impact on his early life and personality of the two dominant females in his childhood.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1rFcosLtBnGL2ru0IPtwx3QSeKK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ouMbyjN1WJKyRqgvwovGl58e4eR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oliver!</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0063385</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Oliver!</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Musical adaptation of Charles Dickens' Oliver Twist, a classic tale of an orphan who runs away from the workhouse and joins up with a group of boys headed by the Artful Dodger and trained to be pickpockets by master thief Fagin.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5QbZEHndREQxcoGC5TKY8KxBdqa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wGUbzVfuDmqzOu7NZNl8nkWvJll.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>On the Buses</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0067528</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>On the Buses</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Stan gets a little annoyed when his Mum and Sister keep buying expensive items on hire purchase, but the money he earns for overtime working as a bus driver means that he can afford it... just! His job is secure, as bus drivers are hard to come by, and his overtime prospects are good, until the bus company decide to revoke a long standing rule and employ women bus drivers. Aghast at the thought of</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fKIcELUNmiSlktMelhsslPZkxnH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7Lm2F1oxm8Eu6Y0efSYE12hotIK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Once Upon a Time in the Midlands</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0301684</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Once Upon a Time in the Midlands</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Dek, a decent but somewhat dull man, enjoys a happy existence with beloved girlfriend Shirley. They live together with her 12-year-old, Marlene: her daughter by the delinquent Jimmy, who flew the coop years ago and hasn't been heard from since. Dek loves Shirley so much that he proposes to her on national television.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z4w08dm44L650QCegJQML4AyFTJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hD4Ok3fWe9gpGQlunPcCOO79Hlq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pink Floyd: The Wall</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084503</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pink Floyd: The Wall</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A troubled rock star descends into madness in the midst of his physical and social isolation from everyone.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aElHyIdF5jmctFGhlhhaPFsbBJC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tA8Kl83oyv19pQAjpj4JhVt6yEk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pride</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3169706</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pride</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1984, a group of LGBT activists decide to raise money to support the National Union of Mineworkers during their lengthy strike. There is only one problem: the Union seems embarrassed to receive their support.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Kc3vbqO0X4VRnjACGNoWLNQvHo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tqLjEqOELHek2zfZ1d3vknG7Dfu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Quadrophenia</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079766</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Quadrophenia</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on the 1973 rock opera album of the same name by The Who, this is the story of 60s teenager Jimmy. At work he slaves in a dead-end job. While after, he shops for tailored suits and rides his scooter as part of the London Mod scene.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4sRR3pvrAZMG7GEvnR9XzqyHHfD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n31i51vwTOOUxKd1DWU2r6if0XR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rise of the Footsoldier</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0901507</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rise of the Footsoldier</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rise of the Footsoldier follows the inexorable rise of Carlton Leach from one of the most feared generals of the football terraces to becoming a member of a notorious gang of criminals who rampaged their way through London and Essex in the late eighties and early nineties.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k8lbsM0Nl0c1Qp7NnARWjS6TTRA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7uFcnzXTRpSax0QqF8lT1VWPNFO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091859</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rita and Sue are two teenagers living on a run-down council estate in Bradford, who both share a job babysitting for Bob and Michelle's children.  Whilst giving them a lift home one night, Bob decides to take Rita and Sue up to a deserted, country-side landscape.  Clearly knowing what he has in mind, Rita and Sue are only too happy to oblige and both have a sexual encounter with him that becomes a regular occurrence.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bNofq5QmwFeFTILeUOzwG9hPe1X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4tFuICuWhcHSFbQZMGwQOVExO7W.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Saturday Night and Sunday Morning</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054269</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Saturday Night and Sunday Morning</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A 22-year-old factory worker lets loose on the weekends: drinking, brawling, and dating two women, one of whom is older and married.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fHHKxB71EzVzny3ZakxZRGe5Evw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tastycTYBJkloAVcZgjdeYnc1Fo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Scum</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079871</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scum</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Powerful, uncompromising drama about two boys' struggle for survival in the nightmare world of Britain's notorious Borstal Reformatory. [This is the feature film version Alan Clarke made after the BBC banned the original before its scheduled TV broadcast (see Scum (1977)].</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7jgzCmnF4QwRGbv2ubK9VIOAkJp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aLwCAYMGhjx2TgSRvEbLUFg3sJc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Secrets & Lies</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117589</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Secrets & Lies</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>With both her adoptive parents now dead, a black optometrist decides to make contact with her birth mother, but is shocked to find out that she is white.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mfWfW6DfD4oBTFmGAndaTkuPUO5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jwooOYB5zcpoWTFwLYXK4nxFH2E.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sense and Sensibility</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114388</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Sense and Sensibility</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on Jane Austen's classic novel of the Dashwood sisters, sensible Elinor and passionate Marianne, whose chances at marriage seem doomed by their family's sudden loss of fortune.  When Henry Dashwood dies unexpectedly, his estate must pass on by law to his son from his first marriage, John and wife Fanny. But these circumstances leave Mr. Dashwood's current wife, and daughters Elinor, Marianne and Margaret, without a home and with barely enough money to live on. As Elinor and Marianne struggle to find romantic fulfillment in a society obsessed with financial and social status, they must learn to mix sense with sensibility in their dealings with both money and men.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cBK2yL3HqhFvIVd7lLtazWlRZPR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mZfkW31Y9a8DvISpO9nj5Tc7neo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shaun of the Dead</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0365748</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shaun of the Dead</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Shaun lives a supremely uneventful life, which revolves around his girlfriend, his mother, and, above all, his local pub. This gentle routine is threatened when the dead return to life and make strenuous attempts to snack on ordinary Londoners.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dgXPhzNJH8HFTBjXPB177yNx6RI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mrdHbaCp3ysDrzUHle5eQlY9Vzu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Snatch</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0208092</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Snatch</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Unscrupulous boxing promoters, violent bookmakers, a Russian gangster, incompetent amateur robbers and supposedly Jewish jewelers fight to track down a priceless stolen diamond.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/56mOJth6DJ6JhgoE2jtpilVqJO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ysKahAEPP8h6MInuLjr0xuZOTjh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>T2 Trainspotting</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2763304</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>T2 Trainspotting</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After 20 years abroad, Mark Renton returns to Scotland and reunites with his old friends Sick Boy, Spud and Begbie.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xlbpCwa9OXXIiNgXcwuompHFIk9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kR48L1E3OLOkQcnlmpi5wDj7ZZt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The 39 Steps</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0026029</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The 39 Steps</title>
	<year>1935</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Richard Hanney has a rude awakening when a glamorous female spy falls into his bed - with a knife in her back. Having a bit of trouble explaining it all to Scotland Yard, he heads for the hills of Scotland to try to clear his name by locating the spy ring known as The 39 Steps.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/paI9Tmqm2cZG6xy4Tnjw3Ydjuw5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2SCZfhWvFgjmVrpGWN24UpXZVbf.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Bridge on the River Kwai</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0050212</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Bridge on the River Kwai</title>
	<year>1957</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The classic story of English POWs in Burma forced to build a bridge to aid the war effort of their Japanese captors. British and American intelligence officers conspire to blow up the structure, but Col. Nicholson , the commander who supervised the bridge's construction, has acquired a sense of pride in his creation and tries to foil their plans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7paXMt2e3Tr5dLmEZOGgFEn2Vo7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cX4xeWZ0DebcpFoxCXeKbBOZQs4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Commitments</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Commitments</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jimmy Rabbitte, just a tick out of school, gets a brilliant idea: to put a soul band together in Barrytown, his slum home in north Dublin. First he needs musicians and singers: things slowly start to click when he finds three fine-voiced females virtually in his back yard, a lead singer (Deco) at a wedding, and, responding to his ad, an aging trumpet player, Joey "The Lips" Fagan.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eLGW0waiQyEwnNEJcJDH2Tsd3Hu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bQHHEFYBZc23nhbo0z0qB7nxW31.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Day of the Jackal</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0069947</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day of the Jackal</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>An international assassin known as ‘The Jackal’ is employed by disgruntled French generals to kill President Charles de Gaulle, with a dedicated gendarme on the assassin’s trail.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vThgcb3JOj99yETg8WChuci4LV2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eCnT1kEg8uAOyoQLhxoIbqfS0xQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Elephant Man</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080678</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Elephant Man</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A Victorian surgeon rescues a heavily disfigured man being mistreated by his "owner" as a side-show freak. Behind his monstrous façade, there is revealed a person of great intelligence and sensitivity. Based on the true story of Joseph Merrick (called John Merrick in the film), a severely deformed man in 19th century London.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rk2lKgEtjF9HO9N2UFMRc2cMGdj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8dfDnaDKLKxtpvqTQM3F4hMgvOM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Full Monty</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119164</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Full Monty</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Sheffield, England. Gaz, a jobless steelworker in need of quick cash persuades his mates to bare it all in a one-night-only strip show.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xkMiZv2FPrhIAtxvEcN1jAbkHRY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/86k4AcYciKQmqvQm9Eh2hVF3tJ2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Gentlemen</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt8367814</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Gentlemen</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>American expat Mickey Pearson has built a highly profitable marijuana empire in London. When word gets out that he’s looking to cash out of the business forever it triggers plots, schemes, bribery and blackmail in an attempt to steal his domain out from under him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jtrhTYB7xSrJxR1vusu99nvnZ1g.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tintsaQ0WLzZsTMkTiqtMB3rfc8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Guns of Navarone</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054953</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Guns of Navarone</title>
	<year>1961</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A team of allied saboteurs are assigned an impossible mission: infiltrate an impregnable Nazi-held island and destroy the two enormous long-range field guns that prevent the rescue of 2,000 trapped British soldiers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rBnNHKhSHFuac0I6qPYiVLJ6ohy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AsBJ7JjNR7wcONrfkUW027C8D5c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Imitation Game</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2084970</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Imitation Game</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on the real life story of legendary cryptanalyst Alan Turing, the film portrays the nail-biting race against time by Turing and his brilliant team of code-breakers at Britain's top-secret Government Code and Cypher School at Bletchley Park, during the darkest days of World War II.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zSqJ1qFq8NXFfi7JeIYMlzyR0dx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jFp5aAlGQ1H3gwdORL2urr8dnoN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Inbetweeners Movie</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1716772</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Inbetweeners Movie</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>High school graduation just wouldn’t be complete without an un-chaperoned, uninhibited and unforgettable final holiday. At least that’s what Will, Jay, Simon and Neil think when they book a two-week stay on an exotic Greek island. As their dreams of sun-drenched days and booze-filled nights are left hopelessly unfulfilled, the lads fight their way into the party scene with hilariously humiliating results in this smash hit UK raunchy comedy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nePYsVp0qU8EbSXeUdr3xEkHlzN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ffAXhWIgVB9PRxzlDyrDKYckImx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Italian Job</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0064505</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Italian Job</title>
	<year>1969</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Charlie's got a 'job' to do. Having just left prison he finds one his of friends has attempted a high risk job in Torino, Italy, right under the nose of the mafia. Charlie's friend doesn't get very far, so Charlie takes over the 'job'. Using three Mini Coopers, a couple of Jaguars and a bus, he hopes to bring Torino to a standstill, steal a fortune in gold and escape in the chaos.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8NOw3HPHkcBndJW2K6ofbcSb7WD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c7meU9vC9q4umxBUKHpkazP72Wq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Killing Fields</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0087553</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Killing Fields</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The real-life story of a friendship between two journalists, an American and a Cambodian, during the bloody Khmer Rouge takeover of Cambodia in 1975, which led to the death of 2-3 million Cambodians during the next four years, until Pol Pot's regime was toppled by the intervening Vietnamese in 1979.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cX6Bv7natnZwQjsV9bLL8mmWjkS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kjEgZzhigOU6dZKGfw1oVOnmVId.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Last Bus</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt9410034</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Last Bus</title>
	<year>2021</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Widower Tom, on the recent passing of his wife Mary, uses his free bus pass to travel the length of Britain from John O'Groats in Scotland to Land's End in Cornwall, their shared birthplace, using only local buses. It's an incident-fuelled nostalgia trip and his encounters with local people make him a media phenomenon. Tom is totally unaware and to his surprise on arrival at Land’s End he’s greeted as a celebrity.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3BAnsbDaWuyXB4rr8nTtABbAw6t.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ssEPTMOyp87G7OG5fBG2jGSoec5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Long Good Friday</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0081070</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Long Good Friday</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the late 1970s, Cockney crime boss Harold Shand, a gangster trying to become a legitimate property mogul, has big plans to get the American Mafia to bankroll his transformation of a derelict area of London into the possible venue for a future Olympic Games. However, a series of bombings targets his empire on the very weekend the Americans are in town. Shand is convinced there is a traitor in his organization, and sets out to eliminate the rat in typically ruthless fashion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pXS667me5Jfoj1b0xuxgjEMKunF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lQJWAVnPNoXElIPb0t1eKkyndQu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Remains of the Day</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107943</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Remains of the Day</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A rule bound head butler's world of manners and decorum in the household he maintains is tested by the arrival of a housekeeper who falls in love with him in post-WWI Britain. The possibility of romance and his master's cultivation of ties with the Nazi cause challenge his carefully maintained veneer of servitude.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qtwipjmSypSQuSvz5BNirSxZqbg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wqxdhn0WF7Bk3qnrUlF5VivduZu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Theory of Everything</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2980516</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Theory of Everything</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Theory of Everything is the extraordinary story of one of the world’s greatest living minds, the renowned astrophysicist Stephen Hawking, who falls deeply in love with fellow Cambridge student Jane Wilde.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7rIIrOFrbdi2ucAMKoHSaMv8FDN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ke3lanTAgCqPMpOyutIfXzYih2s.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Wicker Man</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070917</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wicker Man</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Police sergeant Neil Howie is called to an island village in search of a missing girl whom the locals claim never existed. Stranger still, however, are the rituals that take place there.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wwtrXRL8SiOWxhwLEvw7iBgYh0g.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xOcVqlNnVUEQhQ3Xqhgh7mqeh9f.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>This Is England</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0480025</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>This Is England</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A story about a troubled boy growing up in England, set in 1983. He comes across a few skinheads on his way home from school, after a fight. They become his new best friends, even like family. Based on experiences of director Shane Meadows.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zzbVtj7qSVLig1sEgGDXJDPhaXF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ldtxkVW93dTVKRrA2Fe0CSl0S1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Threads</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090163</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Threads</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Documentary style account of a nuclear holocaust and its effect on the working class city of Sheffield, England; and the eventual long run effects of nuclear war on civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lBhU4U9Eehr9shstPem6I7BdkxK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bLrrIK9wnJugAo2w0em6cbyzAbA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trainspotting</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117951</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Trainspotting</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Heroin addict Mark Renton stumbles through bad ideas and sobriety attempts with his unreliable friends -- Sick Boy, Begbie, Spud and Tommy. He also has an underage girlfriend, Diane, along for the ride. After cleaning up and moving from Edinburgh to London, Mark finds he can't escape the life he left behind when Begbie shows up at his front door on the lam, and a scheming Sick Boy follows.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bhY62Dw8iW54DIhxPQerbuB9DOP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e9GbzPawXDFvLwSseCXpHkbCyAP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Tyrannosaur</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1204340</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tyrannosaur</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The story of Joseph, a man plagued by violence and a rage that is driving him to self-destruction. As Joseph's life spirals into turmoil a chance of redemption appears in the form of Hannah, a Christian charity shop worker. Their relationship develops to reveal that Hannah is hiding a secret of her own with devastating results on both of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p6PJGuO6K94YylUcAsTTn7Q4cQn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cC4Gtc5mEMV23aPWptM3rZ19nwB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Village of the Damned</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054443</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Village of the Damned</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In a small English village everyone suddenly falls unconscious. When they awake every woman of child bearing age is pregnant. The resulting children have the same strange blond hair, eyes and a strong connection to each other.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qcpXud1UjQzlSe9A062w8Wqgira.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tlQ2OBQAC7woOTZgk1vE9U69vQT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>When the Wind Blows</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090315</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>When the Wind Blows</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>With the help of government-issued pamphlets, an elderly British couple build a shelter and prepare for an impending nuclear attack, unaware that times and the nature of war have changed from their romantic memories of World War II.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQ7CgHdDcKnnzhCXA7wC2JVL7qq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lnOGnHqDlZMRGQTEukwWBu5s7fd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Withnail & I</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0094336</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Withnail & I</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Two out-of-work actors -- the anxious, luckless Marwood and his acerbic, alcoholic friend, Withnail -- spend their days drifting between their squalid flat, the unemployment office and the pub. When they take a holiday "by mistake" at the country house of Withnail's flamboyantly gay uncle, Monty, they encounter the unpleasant side of the English countryside: tedium, terrifying locals and torrential rain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fAaF0qyjJJuAZO7viwYUaO2XNlF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ioY6kNwh1h1syTYu3ppbbYCYmwG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Yesterday</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt8079248</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Yesterday</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jack Malik is a struggling singer-songwriter in an English seaside town whose dreams of fame are rapidly fading, despite the fierce devotion and support of his childhood best friend, Ellie. After a freak bus accident during a mysterious global blackout, Jack wakes up to discover that he's the only person on Earth who can remember The Beatles.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1rjaRIAqFPQNnMtqSMLtg0VEABi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5om2iHhm2dgv0s2YgPDSEMIkRNx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Zulu</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0058777</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Zulu</title>
	<year>1964</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1879, during the Anglo-Zulu War, man-of-the-people Lt. Chard and snooty Lt. Bromhead are in charge of defending the isolated and vastly outnumbered Natal outpost of Rorke's Drift from tribal hordes.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9V7tl1kIb67ZPRRNlUdy3JvqEiA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vIOqw0OBXpSeAxBVYwWqCMrcda8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
