<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="hide-it.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<item>
	<title>Ghost Party</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt13846114</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ghost Party</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mystery</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/OImUIQF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Falling World</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt13374994</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Falling World</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>October 1992. A group of law students head to a remote home upstate where a girl disappeared two years earlier.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/OfFXK7a.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Battlebox</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt14085258</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Battlebox</title>
	<year>2023</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1941, Hong Kong is the Eastern Fortress of the British Empire. With the sudden attack by Japanese forces, three intertwined stories unravel against the backdrop of a collapsing city. First, the story of two Chinese sisters, one who works as a courtesan, the other inside British military headquarters known as the Battlebox, become swept up in a botched spy operation. Second, a tight band of Rajput soldiers on the Gin Drinkers Line becomes trapped in a Japanese ambush, requiring an act of bravery to save the others. Third, an unnerving fog-of-war descends upon Major-General Maltby and his top officers as they struggle with the decision to either fight to the death or offer a humiliating surrender of the British Colony.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/T3dnqOa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Halloween Friends</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt21847522</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Halloween Friends</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Comedy</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/g8mOzZj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Don't Look Deeper</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt22811298</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Don't Look Deeper</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A high school student in central California sets off an unexpected series of events when she begins to doubt if she's human.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/InVfBcA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Bank of Dave</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt14308636</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bank of Dave</title>
	<year>2023</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on the true-life experiences of Dave Fishwick; 'Bank of Dave' tells the story of how a working class Burnley man and self-made millionaire fought to set up a community bank so that he could help the local businesses of Burnley not only survive, but thrive. In his bid to help his beloved community of Burnley he has to take on the elitist financial instutions of London and fight to receive the first, new banking license to be issued in over 100 years. Joel Fry (Yesterday, In The Earth, Love Wedding Repeat), who recently starred as one of the leads in the big budget, family movie Cruella, plays young London lawyer Hugh who is hired by Dave to fight his case against the British banking system. Star of Netflix hit Bridgerton, Phoebe Dynevor (The Colour Room) plays feisty local doctor Alexandra. The character of Dave is played by Olivier winner and BAFTA nominee Rory Kinnear (Bond, Penny Dreadful and The Imitation Game)</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/ypH81g6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>White Noise</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6160448</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>White Noise</title>
	<year>2022</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Dramatizes a contemporary American family's attempts to deal with the mundane conflicts of everyday life while grappling with the universal mysteries of love, death, and the possibility of happiness in an uncertain world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/Bm6Cuk6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.imgur.com/KN7YKvX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
