<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="hide-it.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A Bronx Tale</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106489</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Bronx Tale</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in the Bronx during the tumultuous 1960s, an adolescent boy is torn between his honest, working-class father and a violent yet charismatic crime boss. Complicating matters is the youngster's growing attraction - forbidden in his neighborhood - for a beautiful black girl.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sDbO6LmLYtyqAoFTPpRcMgPSCEO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/krYelh3x8VdSeAqOSd81NTek1aw.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ace Ventura: Pet Detective</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0109040</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ace Ventura: Pet Detective</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>He's Ace Ventura: Pet Detective. Jim Carrey is on the case to find the Miami Dolphins' missing mascot and quarterback Dan Marino. He goes eyeball to eyeball with a man-eating shark, stakes out the Miami Dolphins and woos and wows the ladies. Whether he's undercover, under fire or underwater, he always gets his man… or beast!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pqiRuETmuSybfnVZ7qyeoXhQyN1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9f4CQGz30aqwLxjXNjWku9nGHbo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>American Pie</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0163651</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>American Pie</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>At a high-school party, four friends find that losing their collective virginity isn't as easy as they had thought. But they still believe that they need to do so before college. To motivate themselves, they enter a pact to all "score" by their senior prom.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mMprGx972sf1TCI8gZUIVkicSHc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zoRWvvZEoYvnESG30ubQ9fWhrdk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Animal House</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077975</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Animal House</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>At a 1962 College, Dean Vernon Wormer is determined to expel the entire Delta Tau Chi Fraternity, but those troublemakers have other plans for him.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1iYG1mu8dPIXPzUBZF4OE1KUMMl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bqrIvVL3g1XmcI76JZjnwPImy1L.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Armageddon</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120591</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Armageddon</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When an asteroid threatens to collide with Earth, NASA honcho Dan Truman determines the only way to stop it is to drill into its surface and detonate a nuclear bomb. This leads him to renowned driller Harry Stamper, who agrees to helm the dangerous space mission provided he can bring along his own hotshot crew. Among them is the cocksure A.J. who Harry thinks isn't good enough for his daughter, until the mission proves otherwise.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eTM3qtGhDU8cvjpoa6KEt5E2auU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sODk4VuMTt8S56zYFOr1Kx8BFqu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Avatar</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0499549</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avatar</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the 22nd century, a paraplegic Marine is dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission, but becomes torn between following orders and protecting an alien civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jRXYjXNq0Cs2TcJjLkki24MLp7u.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8I37NtDffNV7AZlDa7uDvvqhovU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Back to the Future</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088763</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Back to the Future</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Eighties teenager Marty McFly is accidentally sent back in time to 1955, inadvertently disrupting his parents' first meeting and attracting his mother's romantic interest. Marty must repair the damage to history by rekindling his parents' romance and - with the help of his eccentric inventor friend Doc Brown - return to 1985.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fNOH9f1aA7XRTzl1sAOx9iF553Q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5bzPWQ2dFUl2aZKkp7ILJVVkRed.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Bohemian Rhapsody</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1727824</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Bohemian Rhapsody</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock 'n' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury's increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lHu1wtNaczFPGFDTrjCSzeLPTKN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7mmXWuBeNJiBO0NIOUWOuFve4Tb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Convoy</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077369</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Convoy</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Trucker Rubber Duck and his buddies Pig Pen, Widow Woman and Spider Mike use their CB radios to warn one another of the presence of cops. But conniving Sheriff Wallace is hip to the truckers' tactics, and begins tricking the drivers through his own CB broadcasts. Facing constant harassment from the law, Rubber Duck and his pals use their radios to coordinate a vast convoy and rule the road.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fhjLa7wysN5kII0AaWmbM6SbUpL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zCEi0jbsDEUZBAunm55ij9Ri0Hz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dead Man's Shoes</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0419677</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dead Man's Shoes</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A soldier returns home to his small town and exacts a deadly revenge on the thugs who tormented his dimwitted brother while he was away.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lI7dsNWL8Ue5n5dB5dAdQhTktPe.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gaCrwIiqB2S0w6xDOSa76NUIawU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Die Hard</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095016</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>NYPD cop John McClane's plan to reconcile with his estranged wife is thrown for a serious loop when, minutes after he arrives at her office, the entire building is overtaken by a group of terrorists. With little help from the LAPD, wisecracking McClane sets out to single-handedly rescue the hostages and bring the bad guys down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yFihWxQcmqcaBR31QM6Y8gT6aYV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rahJyvdMruvqUmSLWRQKYS57mx8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Die Hard 2</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099423</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard 2</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Off-duty cop John McClane is gripped with a feeling of déjà vu when, on a snowy Christmas Eve in the nation’s capital, terrorists seize a major international airport, holding thousands of holiday travelers hostage. Renegade military commandos led by a murderous rogue officer plot to rescue a drug lord from justice and are prepared for every contingency except one: McClane’s smart-mouthed heroics.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/56QECFJxueUVJAppVxwEE9ZDYrn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fgkgab4Rel0nOI3B3scHeNB4Mn6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0112864</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Die Hard: With a Vengeance</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>New York detective John McClane is back and kicking bad-guy butt in the third installment of this action-packed series, which finds him teaming with civilian Zeus Carver to prevent the loss of innocent lives. McClane thought he'd seen it all, until a genius named Simon engages McClane, his new "partner" -- and his beloved city -- in a deadly game that demands their concentration.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lwTE6cUhGxRaJvQ5VPdletIGDPh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qk0A79253qOG8bStPIEN7VEXSij.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dirty Dancing</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0092890</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dirty Dancing</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Expecting the usual tedium that accompanies a summer in the Catskills with her family, 17-year-old Frances 'Baby' Houseman is surprised to find herself stepping into the shoes of a professional hoofer—and unexpectedly falling in love.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9Jw6jys7q9gjzVX5zm1z0gC8gY9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6iDQCBUSZKzY8Rnu8ECwl2gXcfG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dirty Harry</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0066999</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dirty Harry</title>
	<year>1971</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When a madman dubbed 'Scorpio' terrorizes San Francisco, hard-nosed cop, Harry Callahan – famous for his take-no-prisoners approach to law enforcement – is tasked with hunting down the psychopath. Harry eventually collars Scorpio in the process of rescuing a kidnap victim, only to see him walk on technicalities. Now, the maverick detective is determined to nail the maniac himself.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/UHxxkYe9tRdiPu0JFgcEL5hmQ4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ezrb56YdkoG59fZj50IxE9OnADx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>East Is East</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0166175</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>East Is East</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1971 Salford fish-and-chip shop owner George Khan expects his family to follow his strict Pakistani Muslim ways. But his children, with an English mother and having been born and brought up in Britain, increasingly see themselves as British and start to reject their father's rules on dress, food, religion, and living in general.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tDchJ4mB23vGgwdQCmq9FCQ4W23.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dxsMt5JspjPdMk59nap00Z8p4nx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Edge of Tomorrow</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1631867</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Edge of Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Major Bill Cage is an officer who has never seen a day of combat when he is unceremoniously demoted and dropped into combat. Cage is killed within minutes, managing to take an alpha alien down with him. He awakens back at the beginning of the same day and is forced to fight and die again... and again - as physical contact with the alien has thrown him into a time loop.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/90fY4P2VXW7EWg7OUbYnhN631KY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4V1yIoAKPMRQwGBaSses8Bp2nsi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Enter the Dragon</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070034</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Enter the Dragon</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A martial artist agrees to spy on a reclusive crime lord using his invitation to a tournament there as cover.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zN7OOSARMLVzl9xJqkW2CcZ3xhY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6uChT8jRjTwcVo4X5pIUctsl1qN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fight Club</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0137523</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fight Club</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A ticking-time-bomb insomniac and a slippery soap salesman channel primal male aggression into a shocking new form of therapy. Their concept catches on, with underground "fight clubs" forming in every town, until an eccentric gets in the way and ignites an out-of-control spiral toward oblivion.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pB8BM7pdSp6B6Ih7QZ4DrQ3PmJK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hZkgoQYus5vegHoetLkCJzb17zJ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>First Blood</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083944</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>First Blood</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When former Green Beret John Rambo is harassed by local law enforcement and arrested for vagrancy, the Vietnam vet snaps, runs for the hills and rat-a-tat-tats his way into the action-movie hall of fame. Hounded by a relentless sheriff, Rambo employs heavy-handed guerilla tactics to shake the cops off his tail.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a9sa6ERZCpplbPEO7OMWE763CLD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hCxxOJojCUFyuahDx167glJgp7E.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fish Tank</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1232776</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fish Tank</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mia is a rebellious teenager on the verge of being kicked out of school. Her hard-partying mother, Joanne, neglects Mia's welfare in favor of her own, and her younger sister hangs out with a much older crowd. Sparks fly between Mia and Connor, Joanne's new boyfriend, and he encourages Mia to pursue her interest in dance. As the boundaries of the relationships become blurred, Mia and Joanne compete for Connor's affection.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q4Q6ZQzV016w8CGn6idGrtF7h7t.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kUa5p73cjzDXoqB6SKncfYKmMu2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Forbidden Planet</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0049223</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Forbidden Planet</title>
	<year>1956</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Starship C57D travels to planet Altair 4 in search of the crew of spaceship "Bellerophon," a scientific expedition that has been missing for 20 years, only to find themselves unwelcome by the expedition's lone survivor and warned of destruction by an invisible force if they don't turn back immediately.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aq0OQfRS7hDDI8vyD0ICbH9eguC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9EUmwXS6EbY5djAhLtBGzUbBwNV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Four Weddings and a Funeral</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0109831</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Four Weddings and a Funeral</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Over the course of five social occasions, a committed bachelor must consider the notion that he may have discovered love.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qa72G2VS0bpxms6yo0tI9vsHm2e.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ejFaHWnDP29z7ePw2cJVOsWvOvH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Full Metal Jacket</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093058</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Full Metal Jacket</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A pragmatic U.S. Marine observes the dehumanizing effects the U.S.-Vietnam War has on his fellow recruits from their brutal boot camp training to the bloody street fighting in Hue.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kMKyx1k8hWWscYFnPbnxxN4Eqo4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yozBWKbyeXtPGN75PlHurOaVvEz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>GoodFellas</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099685</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>GoodFellas</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The true story of Henry Hill, a half-Irish, half-Sicilian Brooklyn kid who is adopted by neighbourhood gangsters at an early age and climbs the ranks of a Mafia family under the guidance of Jimmy Conway.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aKuFiU82s5ISJpGZp7YkIr3kCUd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sw7mordbZxgITU877yTpZCud90M.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Green Street Hooligans</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0385002</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Green Street Hooligans</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After being wrongfully expelled from Harvard University, American Matt Buckner flees to his sister's home in England. Once there, he is befriended by her charming and dangerous brother-in-law, Pete Dunham, and introduced to the underworld of British football hooliganism. Matt learns to stand his ground through a friendship that develops against the backdrop of this secret and often violent world. 'Green Street Hooligans' is a story of loyalty, trust and the sometimes brutal consequences of living close to the edge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tfLj69EoP1b8ZWfLyg5FGJ5LC38.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qE8b8aCKEoZxDmS6PITSc4EiQ0F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Heartbreak Ridge</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091187</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Heartbreak Ridge</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A hard-nosed, hard-living Marine gunnery sergeant clashes with his superiors and his ex-wife as he takes command of a spoiled recon platoon with a bad attitude.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aMr99UigkMCTSPnLTpkzJeLmpyc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sU8BrL7SVAzeKXpMNL6spYNrJ9s.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Independence Day</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Independence Day</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>On July 2, a giant alien mothership enters orbit around Earth and deploys several dozen saucer-shaped 'destroyer' spacecraft that quickly lay waste to major cities around the planet. On July 3, the United States conducts a coordinated counterattack that fails. On July 4, a plan is devised to gain access to the interior of the alien mothership in space, in order to plant a nuclear missile.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0BPQGSPoSa8Ml0DAf2mB2kCU0R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uw4SnKFZ453Gxmj5XR5Susj8TNo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jackie Brown</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119396</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Jackie Brown</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jackie Brown is a flight attendant who gets caught in the middle of smuggling cash into the country for her gunrunner boss. When the cops try to use Jackie to get to her boss, she hatches a plan — with help from a bail bondsman — to keep the money for herself.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ewbLUXvm4riZL0aepy90o0vMesn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXELcGjyU0osFfUCiz1YdAn470M.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Layer Cake</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0375912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Layer Cake</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When a seemingly straight-forward drug deal goes awry, XXXX has to break his die-hard rules and turn up the heat, not only to outwit the old regime and come out on top, but to save his own skin...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fSE9AI2Ytz2mBZjelc32NiZGcj9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a8230eNW59hSOkj5XrRpzMMh0WT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Life of Brian</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079470</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Life of Brian</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Brian Cohen is an average young Jewish man, but through a series of ridiculous events, he gains a reputation as the Messiah. When he's not dodging his followers or being scolded by his shrill mother, the hapless Brian has to contend with the pompous Pontius Pilate and acronym-obsessed members of a separatist movement. Rife with Monty Python's signature absurdity, the tale finds Brian's life paralleling Biblical lore, albeit with many more laughs.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lSSA64WF0M0BXnjwr2quMh6shCl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gbLeMznYBlI7rsyg766oBwkdo2w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120735</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A card shark and his unwillingly-enlisted friends need to make a lot of cash quick after losing a sketchy poker match. To do this they decide to pull a heist on a small-time gang who happen to be operating out of the flat next door.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8kSerJrhrJWKLk1LViesGcnrUPE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cXQH2u7wUIX1eoIdEj51kHXoWhX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Love Actually</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0314331</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Love Actually</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Eight London couples try to deal with their relationships in different ways. Their tryst with love makes them discover how complicated relationships can be.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7QPeVsr9rcFU9Gl90yg0gTOTpVv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xUWf5xX0AnZgAnYXAMk03zTbsef.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Minority Report</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0181689</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Minority Report</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>John Anderton is a top 'Precrime' cop in the late-21st century, when technology can predict crimes before they're committed. But Anderton becomes the quarry when another investigator targets him for a murder charge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ccqpHq5tk5W4ymbSbuoy4uYOxFI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qq4H9JfBKQ5DarMLI6lhUQjn9D7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071853</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>King Arthur, accompanied by his squire, recruits his Knights of the Round Table, including Sir Bedevere the Wise, Sir Lancelot the Brave, Sir Robin the Not-Quite-So-Brave-As-Sir-Lancelot and Sir Galahad the Pure. On the way, Arthur battles the Black Knight who, despite having had all his limbs chopped off, insists he can still fight. They reach Camelot, but Arthur decides not  to enter, as "it is a silly place".</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8AVb7tyxZRsbKJNOTJHQZl7JYWO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nWkxOXpctN2NuToGzwCSdFdiht0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Northern Soul</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1837613</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Northern Soul</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in 1974, an authentic and uplifting tale of two friends whose horizons are opened up by the discovery of black American soul music.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ajnHRtHP2QUtoJ7VeAVP3E9gaI8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xSmW93b4LhVTbOp4HYRsooCYviI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Once Upon a Time in the Midlands</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0301684</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Once Upon a Time in the Midlands</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Dek, a decent but somewhat dull man, enjoys a happy existence with beloved girlfriend Shirley. They live together with her 12-year-old, Marlene: her daughter by the delinquent Jimmy, who flew the coop years ago and hasn't been heard from since. Dek loves Shirley so much that he proposes to her on national television.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z4w08dm44L650QCegJQML4AyFTJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hD4Ok3fWe9gpGQlunPcCOO79Hlq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pink Floyd: The Wall</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084503</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pink Floyd: The Wall</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A troubled rock star descends into madness in the midst of his physical and social isolation from everyone.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aElHyIdF5jmctFGhlhhaPFsbBJC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tA8Kl83oyv19pQAjpj4JhVt6yEk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Porky's</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084522</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Porky's</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in 1954, a group of Florida high schoolers seek out to lose their virginity which leads them to seek revenge on a sleazy nightclub owner and his redneck sheriff brother for harassing them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AqCOt1cWfKqCepxK7LIdT812idH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7zVPeUgL6pgBmV0H9ptqeMiGHUD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pride</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3169706</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pride</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1984, a group of LGBT activists decide to raise money to support the National Union of Mineworkers during their lengthy strike. There is only one problem: the Union seems embarrassed to receive their support.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Kc3vbqO0X4VRnjACGNoWLNQvHo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tqLjEqOELHek2zfZ1d3vknG7Dfu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pulp Fiction</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0110912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pulp Fiction</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper. Their adventures unfurl in three stories that ingeniously trip back and forth in time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fIE3lAGcZDV1G6XM5KmuWnNsPp1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/suaEOtk1N1sgg2MTM7oZd2cfVp3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Quadrophenia</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079766</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Quadrophenia</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on the 1973 rock opera album of the same name by The Who, this is the story of 60s teenager Jimmy. At work he slaves in a dead-end job. While after, he shops for tailored suits and rides his scooter as part of the London Mod scene.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4sRR3pvrAZMG7GEvnR9XzqyHHfD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n31i51vwTOOUxKd1DWU2r6if0XR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rain Man</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0095953</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rain Man</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When car dealer Charlie Babbitt learns that his estranged father has died, he returns home to Cincinnati, where he discovers that he has a savant older brother named Raymond and that his father's $3 million fortune is being left to the mental institution in which Raymond lives. Motivated by his father's money, Charlie checks Raymond out of the facility in order to return with him to Los Angeles. The brothers' cross-country trip ends up changing both their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iTNHwO896WKkaoPtpMMS74d8VNi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mrfbeWcjgSaZ9NEb0xJMR9xzSeB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rambo: First Blood Part II</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0089880</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rambo: First Blood Part II</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>John Rambo is released from prison by the government for a top-secret covert mission to the last place on Earth he'd want to return - the jungles of Vietnam.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pzPdwOitmTleVE3YPMfIQgLh84p.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iUCNrTKQZRKmKMEMIznm2UlUmEd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Reservoir Dogs</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0105236</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Reservoir Dogs</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A botched robbery indicates a police informant, and the pressure mounts in the aftermath at a warehouse. Crime begets violence as the survivors -- veteran Mr. White, newcomer Mr. Orange, psychopathic parolee Mr. Blonde, bickering weasel Mr. Pink and Nice Guy Eddie -- unravel.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xi8Iu6qyTfyZVDVy60raIOYJJmk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jqFjgNnxpXIXWuPsyfqmcLXRo9p.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Return of the Jedi</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086190</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Return of the Jedi</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Luke Skywalker leads a mission to rescue his friend Han Solo from the clutches of Jabba the Hutt, while the Emperor seeks to destroy the Rebellion once and for all with a second dreaded Death Star.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q6ydU8r1iYyy2bV7tPVaq266Y1k.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/soJdiy91Mcyj29GzEgZ5svFcuZg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rise of the Footsoldier</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0901507</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rise of the Footsoldier</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rise of the Footsoldier follows the inexorable rise of Carlton Leach from one of the most feared generals of the football terraces to becoming a member of a notorious gang of criminals who rampaged their way through London and Essex in the late eighties and early nineties.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k8lbsM0Nl0c1Qp7NnARWjS6TTRA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7uFcnzXTRpSax0QqF8lT1VWPNFO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091859</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rita and Sue are two teenagers living on a run-down council estate in Bradford, who both share a job babysitting for Bob and Michelle's children.  Whilst giving them a lift home one night, Bob decides to take Rita and Sue up to a deserted, country-side landscape.  Clearly knowing what he has in mind, Rita and Sue are only too happy to oblige and both have a sexual encounter with him that becomes a regular occurrence.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bNofq5QmwFeFTILeUOzwG9hPe1X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4tFuICuWhcHSFbQZMGwQOVExO7W.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Road House</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0098206</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Road House</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Double Deuce is the meanest, loudest and rowdiest bar south of the Mason-Dixon Line, and Dalton has been hired to clean it up. He might not look like much, but the Ph.D.-educated bouncer proves he's more than capable -- busting the heads of troublemakers and turning the roadhouse into a jumping hot-spot. But Dalton's romance with the gorgeous Dr. Clay puts him on the bad side of cutthroat local big shot Brad Wesley.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r2hGyhvNneAifk7UpwAYxrkeFO4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mbYvIxLViy9BX4BnlcxLMAV7icN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>RoboCop</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093870</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>RoboCop</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In a violent, near-apocalyptic Detroit, evil corporation Omni Consumer Products wins a contract from the city government to privatize the police force. To test their crime-eradicating cyborgs, the company leads street cop Alex Murphy into an armed confrontation with crime lord Boddicker so they can use his body to support their untested RoboCop prototype. But when RoboCop learns of the company's nefarious plans, he turns on his masters.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hHtOgGb3NihlyRATHlKPaFApbrd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vMGkly71Jm2KwHN407mxheMGUYR.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Saving Private Ryan</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120815</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Saving Private Ryan</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>As U.S. troops storm the beaches of Normandy, three brothers lie dead on the battlefield, with a fourth trapped behind enemy lines. Ranger captain John Miller and seven men are tasked with penetrating German-held territory and bringing the boy home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1wY4psJ5NVEhCuOYROwLH2XExM2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bdD39MpSVhKjxarTxLSfX6baoMP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Scanners</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0081455</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scanners</title>
	<year>1981</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After a man with extraordinary—and frighteningly destructive—telepathic abilities is nabbed by agents from a mysterious rogue corporation, he discovers he is far from the only possessor of such strange powers, and that some of the other “scanners” have their minds set on world domination, while others are trying to stop them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/VTqLdveNXxGsIAZL5I4RliTTt7.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/weKhPC9dCbKOl633anVJFer44sF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Scarface</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086250</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scarface</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After getting a green card in exchange for assassinating a Cuban government official, Tony Montana stakes a claim on the drug trade in Miami. Viciously murdering anyone who stands in his way, Tony eventually becomes the biggest drug lord in the state, controlling nearly all the cocaine that comes through Miami. But increased pressure from the police, wars with Colombian drug cartels and his own drug-fueled paranoia serve to fuel the flames of his eventual downfall.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iQ5ztdjvteGeboxtmRdXEChJOHh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1qM2BYNE11Viby8ImC9LC00DgDr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Scum</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0079871</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scum</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Powerful, uncompromising drama about two boys' struggle for survival in the nightmare world of Britain's notorious Borstal Reformatory. [This is the feature film version Alan Clarke made after the BBC banned the original before its scheduled TV broadcast (see Scum (1977)].</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7jgzCmnF4QwRGbv2ubK9VIOAkJp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aLwCAYMGhjx2TgSRvEbLUFg3sJc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shrek</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0126029</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shrek</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>It ain't easy bein' green -- especially if you're a likable (albeit smelly) ogre named Shrek. On a mission to retrieve a gorgeous princess from the clutches of a fire-breathing dragon, Shrek teams up with an unlikely compatriot -- a wisecracking donkey.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o04jZs5SXhbvhqO4981W7KJXOWZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sRvXNDItGlWCqtO3j6wks52FmbD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shrek 2</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0298148</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shrek 2</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Shrek, Fiona and Donkey set off to Far, Far Away to meet Fiona's mother and father. But not everyone is happy. Shrek and the King find it hard to get along, and there's tension in the marriage. The fairy godmother discovers that Shrek has married Fiona instead of her Son Prince Charming and sets about destroying their marriage.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2yYP0PQjG8zVqturh1BAqu2Tixl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2JoIysXRYYeveJghG1Br53LRoKF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Smokey and the Bandit</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0076729</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Smokey and the Bandit</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A race car driver tries to transport an illegal beer shipment from Texas to Atlanta in under 28 hours, picking up a reluctant bride-to-be on the way.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/w4RqNZtVHB5Uzlnl6zQlMHft7QI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cIK6eSVbzBCxLFM5pTjM8KCexu1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Snatch</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0208092</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Snatch</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Unscrupulous boxing promoters, violent bookmakers, a Russian gangster, incompetent amateur robbers and supposedly Jewish jewelers fight to track down a priceless stolen diamond.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/56mOJth6DJ6JhgoE2jtpilVqJO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ysKahAEPP8h6MInuLjr0xuZOTjh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0796366</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The fate of the galaxy rests in the hands of bitter rivals. One, James Kirk, is a delinquent, thrill-seeking Iowa farm boy. The other, Spock, a Vulcan, was raised in a logic-based society that rejects all emotion. As fiery instinct clashes with calm reason, their unlikely but powerful partnership is the only thing capable of leading their crew through unimaginable danger, boldly going where no one has gone before. The human adventure has begun again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9vaRPXj44Q2meHgt3VVfQufiHOJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q7M0JpPixbEYT8EhnI7wTEMONxz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084726</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>It is the 23rd century. The Federation Starship U.S.S. Enterprise is on routine training maneuvers and Admiral James T. Kirk seems resigned to the fact that this inspection may well be the last space mission of his career. But Khan is back. Aided by his exiled band of genetic supermen, Khan - brilliant renegade of 20th century Earth - has raided Space Station Regula One, stolen a top secret device called Project Genesis, wrested control of another Federation Starship and sets out in pursuit of the Enterprise, determined to let nothing stand in the way of his mission: kill Admiral Kirk... even if it means universal Armageddon.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uPyLsKl8Z0LOoxeaFXsY5MxhR5s.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oXs8kp1oX5N0Mte6U8UUAwmLwt6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Trek Into Darkness</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1408101</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek Into Darkness</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When the crew of the Enterprise is called back home, they find an unstoppable force of terror from within their own organization has detonated the fleet and everything it stands for, leaving our world in a state of crisis.  With a personal score to settle, Captain Kirk leads a manhunt to a war-zone world to capture a one man weapon of mass destruction. As our heroes are propelled into an epic chess game of life and death, love will be challenged, friendships will be torn apart, and sacrifices must be made for the only family Kirk has left: his crew.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eXbCboT5mMv9RH1E7ogzIytN302.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/npDrIM6ZbuD7nUxI7ZzNBxs4IRF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0092007</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>It's the 23rd century, and a mysterious alien power is threatening Earth by evaporating the oceans and destroying the atmosphere. In a frantic attempt to save mankind, Kirk and his crew must time travel back to 1986 San Francisco where they find a world of punk, pizza and exact-change buses that are as alien as anything they've ever encountered in the far reaches of the galaxy. A thrilling, action-packed Star Trek adventure!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xY5TzGXJOB3L9rhZ1MbbPyVlW5J.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wN3dgwkiWSLrMVukPQIeccv5EJ6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Trek: First Contact</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117731</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek: First Contact</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Borg, a relentless race of cyborgs, are on a direct course for Earth. Violating orders to stay away from the battle, Captain Picard and the crew of the newly-commissioned USS Enterprise E pursue the Borg back in time to prevent the invaders from changing Federation history and assimilating the galaxy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vrC1lkTktFQ4AqBfqf4PXoDDLcw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wygUDDRNpeKUnkekRGeLCZM93tA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Star Wars</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0076759</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Wars</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Princess Leia is captured and held hostage by the evil Imperial forces in their effort to take over the galactic Empire. Venturesome Luke Skywalker and dashing captain Han Solo team together with the loveable robot duo R2-D2 and C-3PO to rescue the beautiful princess and restore peace and justice in the Empire.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6FfCtAuVAW8XJjZ7eWeLibRLWTw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aDYSnJAK0BTVeE8osOy22Kz3SXY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>T2 Trainspotting</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2763304</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>T2 Trainspotting</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After 20 years abroad, Mark Renton returns to Scotland and reunites with his old friends Sick Boy, Spud and Begbie.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xlbpCwa9OXXIiNgXcwuompHFIk9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kR48L1E3OLOkQcnlmpi5wDj7ZZt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103064</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Nearly 10 years have passed since Sarah Connor was targeted for termination by a cyborg from the future. Now her son, John, the future leader of the resistance, is the target for a newer, more deadly terminator. Once again, the resistance has managed to send a protector back to attempt to save John and his mother Sarah.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5M0j0B18abtBI5gi2RhfjjurTqb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xKb6mtdfI5Qsggc44Hr9CCUDvaj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Birds</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0056869</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Birds</title>
	<year>1963</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Chic socialite Melanie Daniels enjoys a passing flirtation with an eligible attorney in a San Francisco pet shop and, on an impulse, follows him to his hometown bearing a gift of lovebirds. But upon her arrival, the bird population runs amok. Suddenly, the townsfolk face a massive avian onslaught, with the feathered fiends inexplicably attacking people all over Bodega Bay.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ADoJaT1s9Jlcfx3Tw2MIZ1BMxo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q2XxGMCO8Zey8YDrvQGi8P8ns5F.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Butterfly Effect</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289879</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Butterfly Effect</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young man struggles to access sublimated childhood memories. He finds a technique that allows him to travel back into the past, to occupy his childhood body and change history. However, he soon finds that every change he makes has unexpected consequences.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l3ad5yv0Nn91zYPgeCjTvut2Nqg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aoL6L4PCn89MHTVyMnmjwBFLmWX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Commitments</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Commitments</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jimmy Rabbitte, just a tick out of school, gets a brilliant idea: to put a soul band together in Barrytown, his slum home in north Dublin. First he needs musicians and singers: things slowly start to click when he finds three fine-voiced females virtually in his back yard, a lead singer (Deco) at a wedding, and, responding to his ad, an aging trumpet player, Joey "The Lips" Fagan.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eLGW0waiQyEwnNEJcJDH2Tsd3Hu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bQHHEFYBZc23nhbo0z0qB7nxW31.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Day After</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0085404</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day After</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the mid-1980s, the U.S. is poised on the brink of nuclear war. This shadow looms over the residents of a small town in Kansas as they continue their daily lives. Dr. Russell Oakes maintains his busy schedule at the hospital, Denise Dahlberg prepares for her upcoming wedding, and Stephen Klein is deep in his graduate studies. When the unthinkable happens and the bombs come down, the town's residents are thrust into the horrors of nuclear winter.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ZISRUN27tpAEstCuGRKsH7Wwxe.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AfBGTLp9JtsWNUJC6rP1U1XCPCE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Day After Tomorrow</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0319262</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day After Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After years of increases in the greenhouse effect,  havoc is wreaked globally in the form of catastrophic hurricanes, tornadoes, tidal waves, floods and the beginning of a new Ice Age. Paleoclimatologist, Jack Hall tries to warn the world while also shepherding to safety his son, trapped in New York after the city is overwhelmed by the start of the new big freeze.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kNKy8eJemg6sCAMBgh4xrD0lleX.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fXJhA3pjLMDkHPgZ2GVhRDXA5M3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Day the Earth Stood Still</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0043456</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day the Earth Stood Still</title>
	<year>1951</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>An alien and a robot land on Earth after World War II and tell mankind to be peaceful or face destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x2DquTpLTq54aPFDnqlwY7apCC3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3cxXe9mLoMiIeBxvjRh4lcC2TuK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Empire Strikes Back</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080684</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Empire Strikes Back</title>
	<year>1980</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The epic saga continues as Luke Skywalker, in hopes of defeating the evil Galactic Empire, learns the ways of the Jedi from aging master Yoda. But Darth Vader is more determined than ever to capture Luke. Meanwhile, rebel leader Princess Leia, cocky Han Solo, Chewbacca, and droids C-3PO and R2-D2 are thrown into various stages of capture, betrayal and despair.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2l05cFWJacyIsTpsqSgH0wQXe4V.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dMZxEdrWIzUmUoOz2zvmFuutbj7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Exorcist</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0070047</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Exorcist</title>
	<year>1973</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>12-year-old Regan MacNeil begins to adapt an explicit new personality as strange events befall the local area of Georgetown. Her mother becomes torn between science and superstition in a desperate bid to save her daughter, and ultimately turns to her last hope: Father Damien Karras, a troubled priest who is struggling with his own faith.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4ucLGcXVVSVnsfkGtbLY4XAius8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xcjJ5khg2yzOa282mza39Lbrm7j.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Godfather</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0068646</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Godfather</title>
	<year>1972</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Spanning the years 1945 to 1955, a chronicle of the fictional Italian-American Corleone crime family. When organized crime family patriarch, Vito Corleone barely survives an attempt on his life, his youngest son, Michael steps in to take care of the would-be killers, launching a campaign of bloody revenge.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3bhkrj58Vtu7enYsRolD1fZdja1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tmU7GeKVybMWFButWEGl2M4GeiP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Godfather Part II</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0071562</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Godfather Part II</title>
	<year>1974</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the continuing saga of the Corleone crime family, a young Vito Corleone grows up in Sicily and in 1910s New York. In the 1950s, Michael Corleone attempts to expand the family business into Las Vegas, Hollywood and Cuba.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hek3koDUyRQk7FIhPXsa6mT2Zc3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kGzFbGhp99zva6oZODW5atUtnqi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Godfather Part III</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099674</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Godfather Part III</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the midst of trying to legitimize his business dealings in 1979 New York and Italy, aging mafia don, Michael Corleone seeks forgiveness for his sins while taking a young protege under his wing.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lm3pQ2QoQ16pextRsmnUbG2onES.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zNnjHLDtV8Ti3aworltaeaLMov4.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Green Mile</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120689</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Green Mile</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A supernatural tale set on death row in a Southern prison, where gentle giant John Coffey possesses the mysterious power to heal people's ailments. When the cell block's head guard, Paul Edgecomb, recognizes Coffey's miraculous gift, he tries desperately to help stave off the condemned man's execution.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/velWPhVMQeQKcxggNEU8YmIo52R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l6hQWH9eDksNJNiXWYRkWqikOdu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Inbetweeners Movie</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1716772</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Inbetweeners Movie</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>High school graduation just wouldn’t be complete without an un-chaperoned, uninhibited and unforgettable final holiday. At least that’s what Will, Jay, Simon and Neil think when they book a two-week stay on an exotic Greek island. As their dreams of sun-drenched days and booze-filled nights are left hopelessly unfulfilled, the lads fight their way into the party scene with hilariously humiliating results in this smash hit UK raunchy comedy.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nePYsVp0qU8EbSXeUdr3xEkHlzN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ffAXhWIgVB9PRxzlDyrDKYckImx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Karate Kid</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0087538</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Karate Kid</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Daniel, a fatherless teenager, arrives in Los Angeles and becomes the object of bullying by a gang of karate students when he strikes up a relationship with Ali, the gang leader’s ex-girlfriend, so Daniel asks Miyagi, a master of martial arts, to help him learn karate.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1mp4ViklKvA0WXXsNvNx0RBuiit.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4TRL9t8yOQ74j7jI4dGy7C9OVvC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Karate Kid Part II</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0091326</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Karate Kid Part II</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After discovering that his father is at death's door, Mr. Miyagi sets out to Japan, to see him with Daniel. Upon arriving, Miyagi must confront an old rival. Meanwhile, Daniel encounters a new love, and some new enemies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k0OwgRR6PNu7h3SiqpCbRdZWNaG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fStLMyjMzIGOch0lCgAyZ0mqwly.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Karate Kid Part III</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0097647</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Karate Kid Part III</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Despondent over the closing of his karate school, Cobra Kai teacher John Kreese joins a ruthless businessman and martial artist to get revenge on Daniel and Mr. Miyagi.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zE58VthFwD9vKy1vEDnSYR6loqm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c12c7Rpq4kakQiaZIQgp5aTaDFB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The King's Speech</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1504320</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The King's Speech</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The King's Speech tells the story of the man who became King George VI, the father of Queen Elizabeth II. After his brother abdicates, George ('Bertie') reluctantly assumes the throne. Plagued by a dreaded stutter and considered unfit to be king, Bertie engages the help of an unorthodox speech therapist named Lionel Logue. Through a set of unexpected techniques, and as a result of an unlikely friendship, Bertie is able to find his voice and boldly lead the country into war.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uQ538BfYLDJh3GXlzRZLo0j7PFj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5eb7l7AE2yU0mvb38fR5qLNhDDH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Omen</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075005</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Omen</title>
	<year>1976</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Immediately after their miscarriage, the US diplomat Robert Thorn adopts the newborn Damien without the knowledge of his wife. Yet what he doesn’t know is that their new son is the son of the devil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0LcWxOIoBx0MEZMn8tFcrvDXR1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gw9vOHSYDEuKcNKgQWS2iePcfjk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Pursuit of Happyness</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0454921</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Pursuit of Happyness</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A struggling salesman takes custody of his son as he's poised to begin a life-changing professional career.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f6l9rghSHORkWLurUGJhaKAiyjY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nKOQiWjhv6LXXSR3PiIab3LrKtU.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Rocky Horror Picture Show</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0073629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Rocky Horror Picture Show</title>
	<year>1975</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Sweethearts Brad and Janet, stuck with a flat tire during a storm, discover the eerie mansion of Dr. Frank-N-Furter, a transvestite scientist. As their innocence is lost, Brad and Janet meet a houseful of wild characters, including a rocking biker and a creepy butler. Through elaborate dances and rock songs, Frank-N-Furter unveils his latest creation: a muscular man named 'Rockv'.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3pyE6ZqDbuJi7zrNzzQzcKTWdmN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5DU39tmUzbXtD6UXgm7iZqxpwoV.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Shawshank Redemption</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0111161</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Shawshank Redemption</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Framed in the 1940s for the double murder of his wife and her lover, upstanding banker Andy Dufresne begins a new life at the Shawshank prison, where he puts his accounting skills to work for an amoral warden. During his long stretch in prison, Dufresne comes to be admired by the other inmates -- including an older prisoner named Red -- for his integrity and unquenchable sense of hope.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hBcY0fE9pfXzvVaY4GKarweriG2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wPU78OPN4BYEgWYdXyg0phMee64.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Terminator</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0088247</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Terminator</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the post-apocalyptic future, reigning tyrannical supercomputers teleport a cyborg assassin known as the "Terminator" back to 1984 to kill Sarah Connor, whose unborn son is destined to lead insurgents against 21st century mechanical hegemony. Meanwhile, the human-resistance movement dispatches a lone warrior to safeguard Sarah. Can he stop the virtually indestructible killing machine?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qvktm0BHcnmDpul4Hz01GIazWPr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wh4ze6klUbeichAj603OKZwY1W5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Time Machine</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0054387</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Time Machine</title>
	<year>1960</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A Victorian Englishman travels to the far future and finds that humanity has divided into two hostile species.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cq2kBK4t0ADB3Nc83NQ16TZqCiM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bUA6Fu0C2jGqrjn0A9AJwTRpq41.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Towering Inferno</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0072308</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Towering Inferno</title>
	<year>1974</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>At the opening party of a colossal—but poorly constructed—skyscraper, a massive fire breaks out, threatening to destroy the tower and everyone in it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mFM1GbrRrT3DWUFFo8koSITFnYe.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jeYZKtomLnqrBF1Uqjhy432afqg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Wanderers</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080117</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wanderers</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The streets of the Bronx are owned by '60s youth gangs where the joy and pain of adolescence is lived. Philip Kaufman tells his take on the novel by Richard Price about the history of the Italian-American gang ‘The Wanderers.’</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oedFtX9hZZWpD7L5wkD0WxSteY2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1K9YJzQ6r5nCrOVrjSnAmji8zLc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The War of the Worlds</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0046534</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The War of the Worlds</title>
	<year>1953</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The residents of a small town are excited when a flaming meteor lands in the hills, until they discover it is the first of many transport devices from Mars bringing an army of invaders invincible to any man-made weapon, even the atomic bomb.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gzc75Za4ArqfXIIr7STNnIE5rnA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/842AcW0eLEIagMTXLdbGVSsDHLh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Warriors</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0080120</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Warriors</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Prominent gang leader Cyrus calls a meeting of New York's gangs to set aside their turf wars and take over the city. At the meeting, a rival leader kills Cyrus, but a Coney Island gang called the Warriors is wrongly blamed for Cyrus' death. Before you know it, the cops and every gangbanger in town is hot on the Warriors' trail.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fCDXAJcPvpsMd5CL1kBKkkNGW3X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GDAldgmycOxNfEcycEX9IvVvIk.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Wedding Singer</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120888</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Wedding Singer</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Robbie, a local rock star turned wedding singer, is dumped on the day of his wedding. Meanwhile, waitress Julia finally sets a wedding date with her fiancée Glenn. When Julia and Robbie meet and hit it off, they find that things are more complicated than anybody thought.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zVvyTrcZQb7kC2DPDzyo25WcxXp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7Kfuj85Bbi6EJqfhg2wKUh2fEkN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>This Is England</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0480025</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>This Is England</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A story about a troubled boy growing up in England, set in 1983. He comes across a few skinheads on his way home from school, after a fight. They become his new best friends, even like family. Based on experiences of director Shane Meadows.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zzbVtj7qSVLig1sEgGDXJDPhaXF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ldtxkVW93dTVKRrA2Fe0CSl0S1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Threads</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090163</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Threads</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Documentary style account of a nuclear holocaust and its effect on the working class city of Sheffield, England; and the eventual long run effects of nuclear war on civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lBhU4U9Eehr9shstPem6I7BdkxK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bLrrIK9wnJugAo2w0em6cbyzAbA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trainspotting</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0117951</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Trainspotting</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Heroin addict Mark Renton stumbles through bad ideas and sobriety attempts with his unreliable friends -- Sick Boy, Begbie, Spud and Tommy. He also has an underage girlfriend, Diane, along for the ride. After cleaning up and moving from Edinburgh to London, Mark finds he can't escape the life he left behind when Begbie shows up at his front door on the lam, and a scheming Sick Boy follows.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bhY62Dw8iW54DIhxPQerbuB9DOP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e9GbzPawXDFvLwSseCXpHkbCyAP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Tyrannosaur</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1204340</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tyrannosaur</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The story of Joseph, a man plagued by violence and a rage that is driving him to self-destruction. As Joseph's life spirals into turmoil a chance of redemption appears in the form of Hannah, a Christian charity shop worker. Their relationship develops to reveal that Hannah is hiding a secret of her own with devastating results on both of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p6PJGuO6K94YylUcAsTTn7Q4cQn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cC4Gtc5mEMV23aPWptM3rZ19nwB.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>War of the Worlds</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0407304</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>War of the Worlds</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Ray Ferrier is a divorced dockworker and less-than-perfect father. Soon after his ex-wife and her new husband drop off his teenage son and young daughter for a rare weekend visit, a strange and powerful lightning storm touches down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6Biy7R9LfumYshur3YKhpj56MpB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nH6hPhJq3EEv9CnBZgXU3IQnpJo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>magnet:?xt=urn:btih:100ABF40A2370CD71E9F16461153CC8533476E17&dn=28+Days+Later...+%282002%29+%5B1080p%5D+%5BYTS.MX%5D&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.opentrackr.org%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.leechers-paradise.org%3A6969%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2F9.rarbg.to%3A2710%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Fp4p.arenabg.ch%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.cyberia.is%3A6969%2Fannounce&tr=http%3A%2F%2Fp4p.arenabg.com%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.internetwarriors.net%3A1337%2Fannounce</sublink>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>magnet:?xt=urn:btih:100ABF40A2370CD71E9F16461153CC8533476E17&dn=28+Days+Later...+%282002%29+%5B1080p%5D+%5BYTS.MX%5D</sublink>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>magnet:?xt=urn:btih:100ABF40A2370CD71E9F16461153CC8533476E17&dn=28+Days+Later...+%282002%29+%5B1080p%5D+%5BYTS.MX%5D</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0289043</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>28 Days Later</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>magnet:?xt=urn:btih:100ABF40A2370CD71E9F16461153CC8533476E17&dn=28+Days+Later...+%282002%29+%5B1080p%5D+%5BYTS.MX%5D&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.opentrackr.org%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.leechers-paradise.org%3A6969%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2F9.rarbg.to%3A2710%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Fp4p.arenabg.ch%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.cyberia.is%3A6969%2Fannounce&tr=http%3A%2F%2Fp4p.arenabg.com%3A1337%2Fannounce&tr=udp%3A%2F%2Ftracker.internetwarriors.net%3A1337%2Fannounce</link>
	<summary>Twenty-eight days after a killer virus was accidentally unleashed from a British research facility, a small group of London survivors are caught in a desperate struggle to protect themselves from the infected. Carried by animals and humans, the virus turns those it infects into homicidal maniacs -- and it's absolutely impossible to contain.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sQckQRt17VaWbo39GIu0TMOiszq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/veUl0QT8swshQ9Dz0fQ1k6ZkthD.jpg</fanart>
</item>

